PROFILE

Name: Moushegh Nazaretyan Home Address: Hufnagelstr.1 80686

Munich, Germany

Telephone: +49 152 21605734

Email: moushegh@nazaretyan.com

Birthplace: Yerevan, Armenia

Nationality: Armenian

Work status: EU Permanent Residency

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Setup and maintenance of full featured Linux, Unix or SUN Solaris based servers, solid experience in Windows Setup and maintenance of internet/intranet networks, gateways, routers, proxy and web servers, DNS and DHCP servers

Hardware solutions, like Cisco hardware (Firewalls, Routers, VoIP devices), Nokia firewalls, F5 and Sonicwall Excellent knowledge of software balancing based solutions and traffic shaping, I7 firewall implementation on Excellent knowledge of Ansible and Cfengie, custom server builds for farms and configuration management.

Excellent knowledge of nagios-core based monitoring systems, Munin, Graphite

Linux based systems, software and hardware VPN solutions.

Deep knowledge of IPv4 routing, understanding of IPv6 (tunneling, emulation, 6to4 and 4to6 NAT)

Work experience with Oracle SQL servers and Application servers, MySQL installation, optimization and daily tasks Work experience of DFS (Hadoop, mogileFS) and noSQL (Hypertable, MongoDB)

Practical experience of private content delivery network configuration based on varnish-cache or nginx, high load HTTP video stream caching and redistributing to cache servers.

Good in KVM, OpenVZ, supported XEN and ESXi infrastructures.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2013 – present myra Security GmbH, Munich Germany

Private Company; 1-10 employees; Internet Security industry

Sr. Linux system administrator

- Decentralized CDN network monitoring and graphing.
- Configuration management builds for ansible and later for cfengine
- Custom configuration builds for nginx based on customer needs
- Dealing with data centers and providers for new node installations.
- Remote maintenance for over 100 nodes on different parts of the world
- Security maintenance (security lists participation, "before announce" patches
- 24/7 customer support (3 level) by phone, skype, irc and all other available systems

2012 – 2013 Synopsys GmbH, Munich Germany

Public Company; 5001-10,000 employees; SNPS; Computer Software industry

Sr. Unix system administrator

- Supporting farm of Linux/Unix servers
- Hardware installation and maintenance at colocation
- Supporting office unix/windows infrastructure
- Supporting engineers with SGE/UGE custom configurations
- Bash/perl scripting for configuration management and monitoring

2007 – 2012 insparx GmbH, Munich Germany

Internet Matchmaking Services; 240 employees

Sr. Sytem and Network administrator.

- Supporting c-date.de live infrastructure
- Office and datacenter secure interconnection implementation



- Authentication, Authorization and Accounting support for Live and office environment
- UNIX Based Systems (Solaris, Linux) Administration
- Windows 2003r2 / 2008r2 Systems Administration
- Network Security Systems Design & Implementation
- DB Administration (MySQL Server, postgres replication setup, Hypertable installation and support)
- MogileFS implementation with Nginx and Squid (as a caching service) for huge image database
- 24/7 monitoring system integration and maintenance
- Front-end/back-end server maintenance in live network

2006-2007 **Aviainfotel C.J.S.C.**, Yerevan Armenia

Airport Management Systems

- Total Airport Management Information System (TAMIS)
- Border Management Information System (BMIS)
- "E Visa" visa issue electronic system
- Intelligent Mapping Technology
- Internet Geo-Information System
- Network solution for connecting Ayrum border crossing point to BMIS
- Separation of NSS and Armenia International Airport CJSC networks at the Zvartnots International Airport
- Network solution for Real Estate State Cadastre Committee at the Government of the RA
- SSL Support solution for E-Visa System
- Development of Virtual Private Network for mentioned systems to be accessible from an point of the world

2004-2006 Ministry of Defense of the RA

Armenian Military

Network/System Administrator

- Mail and DNS server administration for www.mil.am
- Security system creation and firewall configuration for all servers in network

2000-2004 Soft Noyan-Tapan

Internet Service Provider

Network/System Administrator and Web-Master

- Development of <u>www.nt.am</u> web page (PHP scripts)
- Development of <u>www.mediaforum.am</u> web page (PHP scripts)
- Development and implementation of traffic billing system
- Network balancing configuration for bast-route based provider use

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Bachelor's degree in particle physics, Yerevan state University, Armenia 2000

PERSONAL NOTES

Age: 30

Married, with 2 children Russian - native language

English - excellent

German - basic knowledge (A2-B1 level)